Guide to the Pi Alpha Xi records,1930-2015.
Pi Alpha Xi records,1930-2015.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Pi Alpha Xi records, 1930-2015.
4379
Pi Alpha Xi.
4.8 cubic ft.
Correspondence, certificates, photographs, leaflets, newsleters.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the national organization. Includes flower judging contest records and photographs, 1978-1986, and copies of Lotus Leaflets (newsletter).
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Ornamental horticulture honorary association.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the national organization. Includes flower judging contest records and photographs, 1978-1986, and copies of Lotus Leaflets (newsletter).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pi Alpha Xi.
Subjects:
Ornamental horticulture--Societies, etc.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Pi Alpha Xi National Report, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Pi Alpha Xi National Report, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Pi Alpha Xi National Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- National Organization, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
- National Member Lists, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Membership Lists, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local Chapters, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9-13)
- Applicatin to Establish a Chapter of Pi Alpha Xi at the University of Tennessee, Knoxville, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Petition to Establish Chapter at Texas Tech, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Lotus Leaf, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Lotus Leaf, Alpha Chapter, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lotus Leaf, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Lotus Leaf, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lotus Leaf, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
- Lotus Leaf, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
- Biographies, 1957-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 25-28)
- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29-31)
- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Manual for Flower Judging, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Intercollegiate Flower Judging Contest, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Competition Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Competition Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Competition Correspondence, 1978-1986, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Agendas, Lotus Leaf, etc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Executive Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Pi Alpha Xi History Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Lotus Leaf (not complete), 1941-1978 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Lotus Leaf, 1980, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Lotus Leaf, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Lotus Leaf, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Lotus Leaflet, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Lotus Leaflet, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Lotus Leaflet, Summer, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Lotus Leaflet, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Lotus Leaflet, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Lotus Leaflet, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Lotus Leaflet, Autumn, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Lotus Leaflet, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Lotus Leaflet, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Lotus Leaflet, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Lotus Leaflet, 2011-2014 (Box 2, Folder 13a)
- Manuals for Flower Judging, 1957, 1975, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Manuals for Flower Judging, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Pi Alpha Xi Convention notes, 1934, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Minutes book (Eta Chapter), 1949-1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Pi Alpha Xi, 1957-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Pi Alpha Xi National (Pres. file), 1963-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Pi Alpha Xi National (Pres. file), 1950-1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Petition for California Polytechnic State University, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Pi Alpha Xi History at WSC [Washington State College]), 1947-1955 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- National Intercollegiate Flower Judging Contest, 1976-1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- National Intercollegiate Flower Judging Contest, 1979-1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- National Intercollegiate Flower Judging Contest, 1981-1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Flower Judging Awards, 1982-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Flower Judging Awards, 1984-1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Flower Judging Awards, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Flower Judging Awards Photographs, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Flower Judging Awards Photographs, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Ken Sanderson files, 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Membership Roster, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- PAX Database: Members, 1923-2007 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- PAX Database: by Chapter, 1923-2007 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Texas Tech, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Iowa State, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Mississippi State, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Texas A & M, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Delaware Valley College, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- University of California, Davis, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- University of Nebraska, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Kansas State, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Oklahoma State University, Stillwater, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- University of Wisconsin, River Falls, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- South Dakota State University, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Secretary-Treasurer files, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Flower Judging Contest, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Rituals, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Secretary-Treasurer Report, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Secretary-Treasurer Reports, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Secretary-Treasurer Miscellany, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- New Initiates, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Membership list A-F and deceased members (Rolodex cards) (Box 3)
- Membership list G-Me (Rolodex cards) (Box 3)
- Membership list Mi-Z (Rolodex cards) (Box 3)
- Pi Alpha Xi National: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Pi Alpha Xi National: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Correspondence (Excluding Membership Requests), 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Correspondence and Bills, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Sent, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Received, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Sent, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Received, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
- Correspondence Received, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Second and Third Place Award Certificates (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Honorary Certificates (samples), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- New Initiates, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- National Meeting, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Letters and Minutes to K. Sanderson (copies), 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- PAX National: Minutes and Reports, 1984-1992, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
- PAX National: Membership Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- National Dues, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Chapter Dues, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Chapter Dues, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Dues and Initate Fees (Bank Statements), 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Chapter Dues and New Initiates, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Chapter List and Dues Payment, 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- PAX National: Bank Statements, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- PAX: Financial, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- PAX: Money-Market Account, Auburn, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- PAX: Financial (and Norwest Bank Account), 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- PAX: Financial, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Accounts Payable, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Bills Paid, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Bank Statements, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Stillwater (Oklahoma) National Bank: Receipts, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Stillwater (Oklahoma) National Bank: Miscellany, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Employee ID# PAX, Tax Exempt File (old) [for interest bank account], 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- PAX: Spreadsheets, 1990-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- PAX: Bank Statements, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- PAX: Invoices & Receipts, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- PAX: Audits, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- PAX: Dues Notices Sent, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Finances, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Bank Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- PAX: Financial Reports, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Dues Notices, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Receipts, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Receipts, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Sovereign Bank Statements, 2001-2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Penn State Account Information, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Order Acknowledgement Forms, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Pi Alpha Xi History, 1931-1933 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- National Constitution (Old) [revised, 1986], 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Constitution & By-Laws, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Rules & Regulations Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- New Ritual (article about Lotus plant), 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- PAX Secretary/Treasurer Duties/Reminders, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- PAX: Chapter Data 1995 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- PAX: Key PMT & AFE logo, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 26)
- PAX: Jewelry, 1985-1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Tassels & Cords, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- PAX Mailing List: Chapters, Board of Directors, 1986-1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Current Mailing List, -1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Flower Judging Awards brochure & Miscellaneous Flower Judging Information, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- PAX: Flower Judging Travel, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- New Chapters, 1990-2004 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Pi Alpha Xi: Utah Petition, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Pi Alpha Xi, 1991-2003 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- New Initiates, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- New Initiates, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Scholarships, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Coaches Award (Old), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Membership Lists (Old), 1949-2004 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- PAX: Hard copies of files, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- PAX: leaflets, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 42)
- PAX: Membership & Lotus Leaf from Ken Sanderson, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- PAX: Records, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- PAX: Records, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Doug Needham's Mac Files (transferred to CD), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Terri Starman's IBM Files (transferred to CD), 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Pi Alpha Xi (transferred to CD), 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Fraternity poster, Undated (Folder 1)
- Membership list, 1966-1967 (Folder 1)